// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the name of the boy who was a soccer star?",
    answer: "Simo",
    options: [
      "Simo",
      "Vuyo",
      "Thabo",
      "Messi"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the nickname that Simo's father gave Simo?",
    answer: "Messi",
    options: [
      "Ronaldo",
      "Ronaldihno",
      "Messi",
      "Massy"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Lionel Messi is a soccer star from wich Country?",
    answer: "Argentina",
    options: [
      "Argentina",
      "Portugal",
      "South Africa",
      "England"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Where did the coach first saw Simo Playing soccer?",
    answer: "At his home backyard",
    options: [
      "At his school sports ground",
      "Near the road",
      "At the sports field",
      "At his home backyard"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Where was the coach coming from when he saw Simo playing?",
    answer: "Coming from practice at the sports ground",
    options: [
      "Coming from practice at the sports ground",
      "From his home",
      "From the shops",
      "Coming from the local school"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What did the coach do after seing Simo play outside?",
    answer: "He invited Simo to come join his team",
    options: [
      "He continued on his way home",
      "He invited Simo to come join his team",
      "He went back to the sports ground",
      "He shouted 'Go boy!'"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "On what day was the match betwwen the two teams?",
    answer: "Saturday",
    options: [
      "On a Sunday",
      "On a Monday",
      "On a Tuesday",
      "On a Saturday"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the colour of the Jersey Simo's team was wearing?",
    answer: "Blue",
    options: [
      "Yellow",
      "Blue",
      "Orange",
      "Red"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the colour of the soccer boots Simo's father bought him?",
    answer: "Black",
    options: [
      "Black",
      "Blue",
      "Orange",
      "Red"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How was Simo feeling at the beginning of the game?",
    answer: "Scared",
    options: [
      "Scared",
      "Happy",
      "Sad",
      "Angry"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "How did Simo play at the beginning of the game?",
    answer: "He was too bad at controlling the ball",
    options: [
      "He was very good at controlling the ball",
      "He was too bad at controlling the ball",
      "He tried his best",
      "He was very impressive at controlling the ball"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What did Simo's father tell Simo after seing he was afraid?",
    answer: "Do not be afraid, do your best son!",
    options: [
      "You disapoint me son!",
      "Let's go home since you are embarasing yourself!",
      "Do not be afraid, do your best son!",
      "Do not to your best, just quite!"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "How did Simo feel after his father encouraged him?",
    answer: "He felt good and wanted to be better",
    options: [
      "He did not listed and continued playing",
      "He felt sad and wanted to go home",
      "He felt bad and wanted to cry",
      "He felt good and wanted to be better"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "With howmany goals did Simo's team win the game by?",
    answer: "4-2",
    options: [
      "4-2",
      "5-1",
      "6-0",
      "4-0"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "What lesson did Simo learn",
    answer: "He learned that to win you must not be scared, but calm down and be your best!",
    options: [
      "He learned that to win you must not be scared, but calm down and be your best!",
      "He learned that you can be scared, and continue with being bad at what you do",
      "He learned that you must run home when you are feeling scared",
      "He learned that to win you must be scared, not calm down and not be your best!"
    ]
  },

  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];
